walyou.com 2019-03-13

# Privacy Policy - Walyou

**Walyou Privacy & Cookie Policy**

At Walyou.com we respect your privacy and are committed to maintaining policies which keep your privacy intact while browsing our website. The following information details our practices in regards to browsing the site, information gathering and more valid details as to our visits. Please read this Privacy & Cookie Policy carefully before using or proceeding to access Walyou.com.  
 ** _Your use of this website indicates you have read and understood this Privacy Policy and indicates your agreement to abide by the terms herein._**

 **Tracking, Log Files & Analytics**

Like many other websites, Walyou.com makes use of log files and analytics applications ( such as Google Analytics) . The information inside the log files or analytics data includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and other analytics metrics.We use Google Analytics (https://www.google.com/analytics) to analyze the use of the Site. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about the Site use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to the website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html

 **Email**

We do not have your email address unless it was provided to us in one of the following ways:Post comments: if you have commented on a post, an email address must be provided, yet it is not visible to the public nor is it shared with external sources. Such comments may also be displayed on a collaborating site (during Giveaway, Contests or Campaigns), yet no personal email identification will be present. Comments may also be removed if deemed offensive, abusive, interruptive, or for other requirements seemed necessary for the well being of the community and its members.  
Walyou Newsletter: when subscribing to our Free Newsletter, you provide a valid email to receive the updates, yet this is also not shared with an external organization or commercial use.

 **Cookies**

Walyou.com use cookies to personalize content and ads and to analyze our traffic. Our collaborators and business partners may use cookies on our site such as advertisements, which maintain whether you have visited the site before or not. We do not have control over these cookies after permission to advertisers have been granted. However, no identifiable information is attached to such cookies.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Advertisements**

We employ external ad service companies for the display of advertisements on our site. Some of the ads displayed may used cookies, but we do not have personal details or access to personal information.

Walyou.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
Various advertisers we employ are Google Adsense, Technorati Media, etc. Since we display Google AdSense, we in fact must inform that Google AdSense uses DoubleClick Dart cookie, as to provide ‘ads tailored to your interests’. In order to provide additional details, we have added a direct link for further information regarding DoubleClick Dart cookie and Google AdSense Privacy Policy and means to opt out of DoubleClick Dart cookie.

If you would like more information about this practice or you would like to explore your options for not having this information used by these companies, visit this website: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

 **Contests/Giveaways**

Walyou runs occasional Giveaways and/or Contests collaborating with various Worldwide companies. Walyou acts only as a publisher in a new Giveaway and/or Contest by the method of a post/article on the site www.walyou.com and contacting selected winners to inform about their prize/s.

Terms and conditions are always present on every such Giveaway, where participants must follow the rules in order to enter and become eligible. Winners are selected in random from eligible participants and emailed directly. Walyou is not responsible for lost emails, those not received and communication problems incurred by ISP and/or Network provider. Unless we hear back based on terms stated in the Giveaway, additional winner/s will be selected without a need to provide prize/s to previous participants.

As in the actual prizes:  
Walyou does NOT own the prizes, does NOT ship the prizes, nor are we responsible for item’s condition, utility or durability. Moreover, any shipment fees and conditions deemed by the company providing the prize is the sole responsibility of the selected winner.

 **External Links**

This Website includes links to external sites as well including product sales. Walyou is not responsible for external websites’ privacy policies, practices, content of such Websites or prices changes.

 **Security**

We take appropriate steps to ensure data privacy and security including through various hardware and software methodologies. However, we cannot 100% guarantee the security of any information that is disclosed online.

 **Disclaimer**

Walyou provides content that is informational and opinion based content for Entertainment purposes only. While we may hope to provide the most updated and accurate information, Walyou makes no representation to accuracy, up-to-date, compatibility or validity of the content, and will not be liable or held accountable for errors, loss, injury or damage arising from its presence at Walyou. If inquiring further specific details, it is always recommended to find official documentation provided by company, product or brand interested in.

For further information or to reach us, we may be contacted at contact@walyou.com.

This policy may be updated at any time and may be found on the site. We encourage your feedback, opinions, and suggestions, these may be forwarded to contact@walyou.com

Updated May 24, 2018
